<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stream &#39;n Share</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stream &#39;n Share</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 18:27:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PUBG And Fortnite Failed Approval in China</title>
      <link>/post/pubg-and-fortnite-failed-approval-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 18:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pubg-and-fortnite-failed-approval-in-china/</guid>
      <description>PUBG And Fortnite, alongside various other games have failed to be approved in China. Images are circulating that list several high profile games that the Chinese Online Ethics Review Committee have reviewed and determined to have ethical infractions, alongside the suggested &amp;ldquo;Recommended Actions&amp;rdquo;. 20 games have been reviewed, with 9 of them failing to be approved:
Stream &amp;lsquo;n Share has reached out to both Epic Games and Blizzard for comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bethesda Data Breach Reveals Customer Information (Updated)</title>
      <link>/post/bethesda-data-breach-reveals-customer-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 01:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bethesda-data-breach-reveals-customer-information/</guid>
      <description>After a trialling week, Bethesda has once again found themselves in hot water. Their support page for Fallout 76 Power Armor Edition users was found to be publicly leaking sensitive user information, including receipts which could contain emails, home addresses and even the card used to purchase the game.
So far, Bethesda has yet to respond on any public channels, only through a forum reply saying “Hi guys, we’ve resolved this issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bethesda Planning Replacement Power Armor Edition Canvas Bags</title>
      <link>/post/bethesda-planning-replacement-power-armor-edition-canvas-bags/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bethesda-planning-replacement-power-armor-edition-canvas-bags/</guid>
      <description>Bethesda has released a statement regarding the disappointing bags that were included with Fallout 76 Power Armor Edition:
We are finalizing manufacturing plans for replacement canvas bags for the Fallout 76: Power Armor Edition. If you purchased the CE, please visit https://t.co/S5ClEZuQrx and submit a ticket by Jan. 31, 2019. We’ll arrange to send you a replacement as soon as the bags are ready.
&amp;mdash; Bethesda Support (@BethesdaSupport) December 3, 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bethesda Bans Fallout 76 RP&#39;ers &#39;Gay Eliminators&#39;</title>
      <link>/post/bethesda-bans-fallout-76-rpers-gay-eliminators/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bethesda-bans-fallout-76-rpers-gay-eliminators/</guid>
      <description>Bethesda has issued lifetime bans to a group of player RP&amp;rsquo;ing as &amp;lsquo;Gay Eliminators&amp;rsquo;, hunting down other players and killing them. In a Twitter post, user @twitch_ajpls posted:
Called themselves the &amp;quot;gay eliminators&amp;quot; &amp;quot;cleansing the wasteland of the queers&amp;quot; &amp;quot;know what we did to your people back then, we killed them&amp;quot; THIS is the stuff said to us tonight when playing Fallout. @bethesda @BethesdaStudios @Fallout #Fallout #Fallout76 pic.twitter.com/zwPuz7AbsG
&amp;mdash; AJpls (@twitch_ajpls) November 16, 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Publishes New Game Content Guidelines</title>
      <link>/post/nintendo-publishes-new-game-content-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nintendo-publishes-new-game-content-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Nintendo have published new content guidelines for online video and image sharing:
 &amp;ldquo;We are humbled every day by your loyalty and passion for Nintendo&amp;rsquo;s games, characters and worlds, and respect that you want to be able to express yourself creatively by sharing your own original videos and images using content from our games.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;As long as you follow some basic rules, we will not object to your use of gameplay footage and/or screenshots captured from games for which Nintendo owns the copyright (&amp;ldquo;Nintendo Game Content&amp;rdquo;) in the content you create for appropriate video and image sharing sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Square Enix Pulls Mobile Games From Belgium</title>
      <link>/post/square-enix-pulls-mobile-games-from-belgium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 15:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/square-enix-pulls-mobile-games-from-belgium/</guid>
      <description>Square Enix has decided to pull three mobile games from Belgium. Recently Belgiums gaming commission concluded that loot boxes were in direct violation of their gambling laws.
The three games are:
Mobius Final Fantasy
Kingdom Hearts Union X
Dissidia Final Fantasy Opera Omnia
Sources:
https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/21/square-enix-pulls-games-mobius-final-fantasy-belgium-loot-box-ban</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubisoft Reverts Rainbow Six Siege Changes</title>
      <link>/post/ubisoft-reverts-rainbow-six-siege-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 21:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ubisoft-reverts-rainbow-six-siege-changes/</guid>
      <description>Ubisoft has decided to revert the controversial changes recently made to Rainbow Six Siege which affected several visual in-game elements.
In a recent update, Ubisoft stated that:
 &amp;ldquo;On November 2nd, we shared an article detailing the Aesthetic Changes coming with Operation Wind Bastion. Since then, our community and players have raised concerns.
We have spent the last week working on solutions and have decided that we will be reverting all aesthetic changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In This Week: 19th-23rd November 2018</title>
      <link>/post/in-this-week/in-this-week-19th-23rd-november-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 11:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/in-this-week/in-this-week-19th-23rd-november-2018/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to In This Week, a roundup segment that features smaller stories that didn&amp;rsquo;t make it into their own dedicated story.
MaoMao Removed From Steam MaoMao has been removed from Steam, the developers state that:
 &amp;ldquo;The game was be removed but I don&amp;rsquo;t know what happened. We don&amp;rsquo;t receive any message about that. Maybe it is ths mosaics problem, so we will soon to solve that. and release the original CG by other method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valve Discontinues Steam Link</title>
      <link>/post/valve-discontinues-steam-link/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 02:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/valve-discontinues-steam-link/</guid>
      <description>Valve has appeared to have completely discontinued the Steam Link. On the official store page, Valve states that:
 &amp;ldquo;The supply of physical Steam Link hardware devices is sold out. Moving forward, Valve intends to continue supporting the existing Steam Link hardware as well as distribution of the software versions of Steam Link, available for many leading smart phones, tablets and televisions.&amp;rdquo;
 Below is a link to where you can find more information about the Steam Link application:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OBS Voicemeeter Audio Setup</title>
      <link>/post/obs-voicemeeter-audio-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 21:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/obs-voicemeeter-audio-setup/</guid>
      <description>This section will cover setting up Voicemeeter Banana Pro with OBS using both Voicemeeter Banana Pro and Virtual Audio Cables. Please note that in order to continue with this tutorial, you will need additional software (linked below) which does require a donation to the creator of said software.
Requirements:
Voicemeeter Banana Pro (Website)
Virtual Audio Cables (required donation for complete setup, one free cable download)
Once you gone ahead and donated, you should recieve an email with a link for the two additional cables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTuber Shirrako Suspended Over Red Dead Redemption Video (updated)</title>
      <link>/post/youtuber-shirrako-suspended-over-red-dead-redemption-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 20:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/youtuber-shirrako-suspended-over-red-dead-redemption-video/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Shirrako has found himself suspended from YouTube after one of his videos entitled &amp;ldquo;Red Dead Redemption 2 - Beating Up Annoying Feminist&amp;rdquo; which featured his character punching the NPC in the face went viral with over 1.5 million views, causing several major outlets to report on the video and criticise the game and the YouTube comment section.
After reviewing Shirrakos account, YouTube determined that the video featured &amp;ldquo;gratuitious violence&amp;rdquo;, which is not acceptable on their site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallout 76 Beta Missing Client Side Authentication Making Cheating Easy</title>
      <link>/post/fallout-76-beta-missing-client-side-authentication-making-cheating-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 22:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/fallout-76-beta-missing-client-side-authentication-making-cheating-easy/</guid>
      <description>Fallout 76 has already become the target of hackers, despite only recenting enter beta. wallhax.com shows off a rather feature rich tool including a 2D radar, field of view correction, stick to target fuction as well as other features, which they claim will be &amp;ldquo;available at launch&amp;rdquo;.
Reddit user teetharejustdone detailed how the game fails to verify the intergity of game files, leading to the ability to mod the game and potentially use the engines features to exploit game mechanics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IGN Nintendo Editor Filip Miucin Plagerises YouTuber Deadite in Dead Cells Review</title>
      <link>/post/ign-nintendo-editor-filip-miucin-plagerises-youtuber-deadite-in-dead-cells-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ign-nintendo-editor-filip-miucin-plagerises-youtuber-deadite-in-dead-cells-review/</guid>
      <description>IGN Nintendo Editor Filip Miucin recently published his video review for Dead Cells, his first ever video review for the site. YouTuber Deadite, who hosts the YouTube channel Boomstick Gaming, found that the video review in question was eerily similar to his own review. Below is a side by side comparsion by Deadite, showcasing the most egregious plagerisms, as well as a tweet from Philip Miucin:
Finishing up my Dead Cells review this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOG Retracts Postal 2 Tweet After Pressure, Classifies GamerGate as an Abusive Movement</title>
      <link>/post/gog-retracts-postal-2-tweet-after-pressure-classifies-gamergate-as-an-abusive-movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gog-retracts-postal-2-tweet-after-pressure-classifies-gamergate-as-an-abusive-movement/</guid>
      <description>GOG recently advertised the newly released Postal 2: Paradise Lost for their online distribution store, prompting some users to fire backlash back at GOG. The tweet in question shows a gravestone noting the date of the now infamous day that multiple gaming press outlets simultaneously published &amp;ldquo;Gamers Are Dead&amp;rdquo; articles, which helped give rise to the GamerGate movement which seeked to restore ethical journalistic policies for said outlets.
After various Twitter users fired backlash towards GOG, GOG pulled the tweet in question and issued the below apology, sparking even more backlash from GamerGate supporters over GOGs apparent lack of understanding about the movement, and the mischaracterisation of the movement in general:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian Senate Bill to Stop Bans on Gaming</title>
      <link>/post/australian-senate-bill-to-stop-bans-on-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/australian-senate-bill-to-stop-bans-on-gaming/</guid>
      <description>Australian senator David Leyonhjelm has introduced the Freedom of Speech Legislation Amendment proposal, which would amend the Classification (Publications, Films and Computer Games) Act 1995 to:
 Remove the ban on publications, films and computer games that offend against standards of morality, decency and propriety.
 And also amend the Broadcasting Services Act 1992 to:
 Remove bans on broadcasting, datacasting and online content, with a specific focus on bans affecting services provided behind paywalls; narrow the guidance provided by government to broadcasting industries and datacasting licensees in the development of codes of practice; remove certain restrictions on subscription television broadcasters and online content services relating to programs or content that has been or would be classified as X 18+, ‘category 1 restricted’ or ‘category 2 restricted’; and remove a ban on broadcasting electoral advertising relating to a federal, state, territory or local election on election day or on the preceding Thursday or Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Germany Bans Pre Orders Without Set Release Dates</title>
      <link>/post/germany-bans-pre-orders-without-set-release-dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/germany-bans-pre-orders-without-set-release-dates/</guid>
      <description>The Higher Regional Court of Munich has ruled that pre-orders with &amp;ldquo;vague&amp;rdquo; release dates are illegal.
The issue was brought to the regional court by a German rights advocacy group, who sued Mediamarkt for illegal information in the online ordering of a smartphone.
According to the judgement, indeterminate statements regarding the delivery of online goods and orders violates the legal duty of information of the seller. The customer is entitled to a specific delivery date before clicking on the order button, and information such as &amp;ldquo;soon to be available&amp;rdquo; are in violation of the consumers rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publishing Guidelines</title>
      <link>/post/publishing-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/publishing-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Below are the publishing guidelines for articles on Stream &amp;lsquo;n Share. Please refer to these guidelines if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in writing for us. Any articles that don&amp;rsquo;t meet these standards will not be published. For reference, check out any of the articles on the main page.
All articles on Stream &amp;lsquo;n Share will allow the author to link their stream link directly to the article in question for additional exposure like so:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ArenaNet Fires Narrative Writer Jessica Price</title>
      <link>/post/arenanet-fires-narrative-writer-jessica-price/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/arenanet-fires-narrative-writer-jessica-price/</guid>
      <description>ArenaNet has fired Narrative Writer Jessica Price over several tweets that were post on the 4th and 5th of July 2018 in response to suggestions from @DeroirGaming, a Guild Wars 2 YouTuber and Streamer. You can find the Twitter threads and comments below:
thanks for trying to tell me what we do internally, my dude 9_9
— Jessica Price (@Delafina777) July 4, 2018 
Today in being a female game dev:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Happy Few Denied Classification in Australia</title>
      <link>/post/we-happy-few-denied-classification-in-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/we-happy-few-denied-classification-in-australia/</guid>
      <description>We Happy Few, first revealed at PAX East 2015, has been denied classification in Australia. According to the Department of Communications and the Arts, We Happy Few was denied classification because:
 The computer game is classified RC in accordance with the National Classification Code, Computer Games Table, 1. (a) as computer games that &amp;ldquo;depict, express or otherwise deal with matters of sex, drug misuse or addiction, crime, cruelty, violence or revolting or abhorrent phenomena in such a way that they offend against the standards of morality, decency and propriety generally accepted by reasonable adults to the extent that they should not be classified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HuniePop vs the National Center on Sexual Exploitation</title>
      <link>/post/huniepop-vs-the-national-center-on-sexual-exploitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/huniepop-vs-the-national-center-on-sexual-exploitation/</guid>
      <description>HuniePop has found itself under the pressure of The National Center on Sexual Exploitation (also know as Morality in Media, Inc), self-described as &amp;ldquo;The leading national organization exposing the links between all forms of sexual exploitation such as child sexual abuse, prostitution, sex trafficking and the public health crisis of pornography&amp;rdquo;.
The group originated in 1962 and was founded by Father Morton A. Hill, Rabbi Julius Neumann and Rev. Robert Wiltenburg as a neighbourhood organisational effort to combat pornography distribution in their local area under the codename &amp;ldquo;Operation Yorkville&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>